Guide to the George Washington University Publications collection, 1924-2017 RG0154
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Medicine and Health Topics, Series 22
  - Bibliography of Audiotaples and Tape-slide Programs Applicable to Undergraduate Medical Education, Undated; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Computer-based Instruction in Laboratory Science, 1983; Series 22 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Medlab Computer Project Annual Report: 1971-1972, September 1972; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Literature and Clinical Survey for Tests of Specific Endocrine Functions, June 1972; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rehabilitation Potential in Chronic Obstructive Lung Disease, December 31, 1967; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fatal Myocardinal Infarction and the Role of Oral Contraceptives: Texts and Tables (Vol. 1), April 30, 1979; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fatal Myocardinal Infarction and the Role of Oral Contraceptives: Protocal, Manual of Operations and Data Forms (Vol. 2), April 30, 1979; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Report on ECG Processing System in the GWU Hospital Heart Station and Medical Systems Development Laboratory, 1967-1968; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Factors Influencing Compliance in Patients with Ischemic Heart Disease, February 25, 1977; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Computer Analysis of the Left Ventricule Regional Motion of Heart (Part 1), August 30, 1983; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Protocol for the National Exercise and Heart Disease Project: A Collaborative Study, Undated; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Effect of Drugs on Learning and Memory, March 31, 1970; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AIDS in Metropolitan Washington: An Assessment of Community Need, January 1989; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Studies of Pathophysiology of Sickle Cell Disease, Undated; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Submarine Escape: An Annotated Bibliography, June 20, 1972; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Effect of Diving on Collagen Metabolism and Skeletal Tissue Deterioration: Final Technical Report, 1980; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dysbaric Osteonecrosis: An Annotated Bibliography, July 31, 1972; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Literature Summary on Countermeasures, January 1972; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Economic Issues in Organ Substitution Technology, January 1988; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Handbook for Lower Extremity Amputees, Undated; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Resource Guide to Protective Aids, December 1979; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Biostatistical Analysis of the Collaborative Glaucoma Study: Final Report on Contract No. 1-EY-4-2167, May 1977; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Directory of Research Projects: Rehabilitation Research and Training Centers (Selected from the Center's Annual Reports to SRS for 1968-1969), November 29, 1969; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bio-engineering Services to Multiply Handicapped Developmentally Disabled Persons, 1975-1976; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bio-engineering Services to Developmentally Disabled Adolescent, 1974-1975; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The George Washington University Welcomes The Washington, D.C. Dermatological Society, November 24, 1981; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Washington, D.C. Dermatological Society, April 27, 1982; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Preventive Health Services for Children: What States are Learning, 1981; Series 22 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Phase I/II Evaluation of Biological Response Modifiers for the Treatment of Cancer, July 30, 1993; Series 22 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Red Cell Preservation: An Annotated Bibliography, 1970; Series 22 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The George Washington University Medical Center Diet Manual, Third Edition, 1976; Series 22 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Obstetricial Anesthesia Handbook, 1975; Series 22 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Public Policy Dimensions of Artificial Insemination and Human-semen Cryobanking, December 1973; Series 22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Scope of The George Washington University Hospital, Washington, D.C. (Vols. 1-6), 1957-1962; Series 22 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The Scope of The George Washington University Hospital, Washington, D.C. (Vols. 7-11), 1963-1967; Series 22 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Studies from the School of Medicine: The George Washington University, 1937-1938; Series 22 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Studies from the School of Medicine: The George Washington University, 1940-1941; Series 22 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Gelman Library and General Library Studies, Series 23
  - Report on the Task Force on Resource Sharing, June 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Collection Assessment, 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Collection Analysis Project: Interim Report, 1981; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Collection Analysis Project: Final Report, July 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Report on Task Force on Preservation, 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Report on the Task Force on Operating Practices, 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Research Design: Staffing Guide for Army Libraries and Information Facilities, February 6, 1970; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The George Washington University Library, 1973; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A Critique on Standards for Evaluating Library Collections, April 1970; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Critique on Guide to Laws and Regulations on Federal Libraries: Army Technical Library Improvement Studies (Atlis) Report No. 4, Undated; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A Study of the Holdings in Mathematics and Transportation in a Selected Number of Federal Libraries in the Washington, D.C. Area, May 1966; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Information Display Systems Project Interaction Handler Development Summary of Modules, November 1981; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Author List: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology, 1980-1984, 1985; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Author List: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology Reports, 1980-1985, Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Index of Publications: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology, December 1982; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Index of Publications: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology, December 1983; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Index of Publications: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology, 1984; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Index of Publications: GWU Institute for Information Science and Technology, 1985; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Universal Decimal Classification: A Selected Bibliography of UDC Literature, June 1971; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Language of Information Science: Convertibility in Information Systems, January 1971; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Title Analysis of Scienctific Articles: Development of Three Types of Index for the Journal Anthology, December 1965; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Where to Look Next: A Subject Guide to Reference Sources, Workbook for Introduction to Library Science, 1971; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cumulative Document Accession List #4: Innovation Information Center/IIAP, August 1975; Series 23 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Library department publications, 1990-2020; Series 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kiev related publications, 1977-2011; Series 23 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Print catalog of the I. Edward Kiev Judaica Collection, 2003; Series 23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Computer Technology & Military Defense, Series 24
  - A Model of Freely Burning Pool Fires, October 1982; Series 24 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - An Analysis of Rotary Jet Rotor Geometry, January 1983; Series 24 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Effects of Limited-access Highways on Nearby Churches, October 5, 1971; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Air Force Resources Management Program, Undated; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guide Leaflet for the Defenses of Washington, Compiled by Stanley W. McClure, Undated; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Development and Application of a Procedure for Coding Derogatory INformation from 42,500 Personnel, October 8, 1965; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alternative Energy Technologies in Brazil, February 1977; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Communist China and Space, December 1964; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A Comparison of the United States and Soviet Space Programs, June 1965; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Soviet Union and the United States in Space, March 1966; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chromium: An Assessment of U.S. Requirements and Vulnerability, November 1982; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Human Factors Related to Quality and Reliability of Unmanned Spacecraft Components, 1964-1965; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Technology Assessment of Space Stations, May 1971; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joint Institute for Advancement of Flight Sciences: Assessment of Ipad Contributions, February 1985; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Apollo Decision and its Lessons for Policy-makers, January 1970; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Authority of the United States Government to Prohibit of Regulate Private Launching of Rockets and Space Vehicles, Undated; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Legal/Institutional Resources for Aircraft/Airport Noise Abatement: Preliminary Draft, May 15, 1973; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - An Integrated Strategy for Aircraft/Airport Noise Abatement: A Legal/Institutional Analysis of the Noise Control Act of 1972 and Proposals Based Thereon, September 25, 1973; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - A Program of Research and Education in Aeronautics: NASA Cooperative Agreement NCC1-44, September 24, 1985; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Joint Institute for Advancement of Flight Sciences: IDS Technical Advisory Group Project, September 25, 1985; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Digital Bits in Telecommunications, August 5, 1981; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - A Survey of Issues in Computer Network Security, May 1985; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Product Networks: A Unified Theory of Fixed Interconnection Networks, December 1990; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Performance Evaluation of Token-ring Protocol by Analytic and Simulation Methods, June 1990; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Banyan-hypercube Network: A Synthesis of Banyans and Hypercubes, March 1989; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - A Group Discussion Program for Changing Attitudes of Younger Traffic Violators, 1964; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Some New Results in the Statistical Analysis of Stochastic Processes of the Reliabiltiy and Queing Type, December 3, 1974; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Queueing Analyses with TK Solver, 1993; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Designing a Support System for Repairable Items, February 10, 1978; Series 24 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Citizen Group Uses of Scientific and Technological Information in Nuclear Power Cases, August 1973; Series 24 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Policies, Series 25
  - An Evaluation of Techniques for Demand Analysis in State Fish and Game Planning, Undated; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Projecting Demand for Hunting and Fishing, Undated; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Management of Water Resources in Metropolitan Environments: Some Cases from the Washington Metropolitan Area, June 1971; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Planning for Water Resources Management in Metropolitan Environments, November 11, 1967; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Patent Policy, 1968; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Management of Water Resources in Metropolitan Environments: Some Cases from the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1966; Series 25 (Box 1, Folder 6)